This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Maki D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum-gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
This site!
Can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will come a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
After his crew was scattered around the world,
Luffy set off to rescue his brother Ace,
who had been captured by the Navy
and sent to a massive prison known as Impel Down.
On his way down to level five,
a closely guarded floor where the most infamous criminals were held,
Luffy encountered an old acquaintance.
Time for my specialty!
Causing chaos!
Works for me!
Break through the crimson hell!
Buggy's chaos-inducing plan!
Gong-gong!
Woo!
I'm just screwing with you.
I call this my chop-chop emergency escape!
A chop like that should break your skull just fine!
And this one here is my aerial tailspin, ding-tong!
You picked the wrong clown to mess with, monkey!
Don't go, monkey!
No!
Hey, hey, don't touch it!
Damn, you got a lot stronger, didn't you, kid?
I don't know. These guys are pretty tough. Where are they?
Sea monkeys. Blue Gorillas, they're called. Or Blue Gordy for short.
But stay sharp. Should be four more of them left to take the place...
Well, never mind. Guess you got them already.
Either way, I hope that's the last of them. I don't have time to mess around right now.
That guy's a monster. How did he do that?
You came here to let us out, didn't you?
We'll be your best friend, pal. I promise.
Something wrong?
You bet there is. I thought you said only one prisoner escaped.
Yeah, it was just the clown guy.
Pretty sure I saw two guys, but maybe I'm crazy.
And speaking of crazy, five Blue Gorillas got taken down in front of community cell number ten.
On level one? There's no way.
The prisoners down there aren't strong enough to take on even one Blue Gorillas.
What? You broke in here to rescue Ace?
Yep.
Shh. We gotta stay quiet.
I'm not really following your own advice there.
We could well use the keys to our cell if you're not too busy.
Would you shut the hell up? Nobody gives a damn.
Wait, do you know Ace?
Yeah.
And though I can see the resemblance, he made a better impression than you did.
You really think this is the time to throw a party?
How can you plan on beating Luffy and the rest of his crew when you don't have any idea where they are?
Oh, come on. Don't be such a party, Pooper Alvita.
We'll find Luffy when we find him, so just calm down.
If you're looking for Luffy, I can tell you where he is.
There you go. Problem solved.
This fellow here can lead us straight to straw hat any time.
Hold on. Who in the hell are you?
Oh, hello. Sorry for crashing your party.
Anyway, the name's Ace, and as you might guess, I was drawn here by the delicious aroma of your feast.
Thanks for feeding me.
No need to be polite. We're all friends here.
It's a pleasure to make your acquaintance, friend.
Just because you introduce yourself doesn't mean you get to eat my food.
My ship, my banquet, my rules.
So take that meat out of your mouth.
Captain, be careful. That guy is fire fisting.
Just let the man eat. He's from Whitebeard's crew.
The second division commander.
Did you say Whitebeard?
What?
Oh, you guys know the old man, huh?
That's nice. He's a real...
He's sleeping!
After he woke up, we had a few drinks, chatted it up, and became pretty good pals.
So yeah, I think it sucks your brother got thrown in here too.
Kind of stupid of the Navy to do that.
I'm sure Whitebeard will give him hell.
I heard they're keeping Ace on level five.
Could you show me the way to get there?
Not a chance in hell! Go by yourself!
What, do you think I'm your friend now?
In fact, you can die down here for all I care.
So long.
If you don't want to break out of here, I'll just do it on my own.
Okay, but there's ten battleships out there.
I hope you've got a good plan.
That's not good.
All right, I get it.
They must be expecting an attack from Whitebeard.
Guess I picked a bad time.
Ah, maybe I could just lay low.
I'll find someone else then.
So are we getting the key or not?
No, no, I must be imagining things.
What would he be doing with something like that?
Then again.
Well, good luck with your escape.
I gotta get moving.
No, that's gotta be it.
White straw!
Go, go, go!
What's your problem?
Up there!
No, no!
No kidding, because you won't stop yelling so much!
By the way, that's a lovely armlet you've got there, Straw Hat.
Do you think you can give it to me pretty, please?
No, it's a gift from Nami.
What do you want with it?
If you let me have the armlet, I'll show you how to get to this.
Is that a promise?
Sure, just fork it over, kiddo.
Okay, you got a deal.
All right!
First off, let's shake those goggles.
Grab onto my feet, okay?
Your feet.
Good, now start running.
Be careful with those.
Can't have you chop them!
Let's review how Buggy's chop-chop power works, shall we?
When he chop-chops his body to pieces, he can control each part however he likes,
but only within a limited area.
And if his feet aren't close to the ground, he becomes unable to levitate the rest of his body.
Damn, I am one lucky clown!
I got the treasure of a lifetime, and to take it out of this crap hole in one shot!
Captain!
What?
I'm just starting to have second thoughts about this place, that's all.
You sure this is the cave where Captain John kept his hidden treasure,
and the crew he left behind never found it this whole time?
It seems a bit too easy.
Just hold the lantern and keep walking.
Yes, sir.
Now look alive, boys.
The treasure is near, but so is unspeakable danger.
If you let your guard down, even for a second, then death will creep up on you.
There's no telling what kind of monsters will appear, or what vicious booby traps await to kill us all.
Come on, men. Another fine day carving out tunnels awaits us.
Right-o, boss!
Oh, you three must be the new guys.
Nothing like working up a sweat, right, boss? All a man really needs is a pickaxe in his hand and a tunnel to dig.
That's right, and because of our good old-fashioned elbow grease, everyone who comes to this tunnel will smile.
It's liberating!
You know, after all this hard labor, we ought to hit it with the old bilge barge for a-
Ah!
How dare you make me work like one of your lackeys!
Unfortunately, that wasn't the first dead end we hit, and it wouldn't be the last.
We ran all over the Grand Line looking for that treasure.
As if that wasn't crappy enough, my ill-fated treasure hunts brought me straight to a navy post one day, and the bastards threw me in this dump when they captured me.
But maybe it was destiny all along, guiding me to Captain John's treasure.
Step on it, strong.
Hard time to waste it.
Follow me, and we'll be at level two in no time.
Level two? Were you listening to me?
I said I wanted to go to level five!
Ah, don't you know how numbers work?
You gotta go through two to get to five!
Let me explain.
Think of this as an upside-down tower.
The place we're in right now is called level one, which is the first basement floor.
After that, you go to level two and level three and so on.
The deeper you get, the more infamous the criminals are.
They tortured me in the fires of level four a few times, but that's as far as I've gone myself.
Everything else is just things I've heard from other people.
Level five is where they take all the big shots, though.
So in a bounty as high as your brother's, he's gotta be there.
As for what's below level five, well, I've heard some rumors, but the details are scarce.
The theory is the criminals they send down there are so dangerous that they've been completely wiped from history.
Now that I think about it, there's a good chance that's where they took your brother.
But the furthest I can take you is level four, so you're on your own after that.
Thanks, Buggy.
I thought you were a real jerk, but I guess I was wrong.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
A deal's a deal.
And if that arm that leads me to Captain John's treasure, I'm getting a real bargain, kid!
Oh!
I shouldn't have opened my big mouth!
Hey, you know what?
What?
If you got caught, you're a pretty crappy pirate.
What the hell, man?
Give me a break!
The idiot didn't even hear me.
I'm lucky he's so stupid.
That's awesome!
This is a treasure map?
I didn't have a clue.
Bet that'll be really fun.
Sorry, kid, but if you know the truth, I'll have to kill you.
You better take this now in case I forget later.
You know that's a treasure map, and you're still going to give it to me?
Yeah, of course.
Treasure's cool and all, but Ace is more important.
But if you give it to me now, what's to stop me from running off with it and leaving you down here to die?
Nothing, I guess.
But you gave your word you'd help out, and that's good enough for me.
Ha ha!
Those trusty eyes, pouring into my soul!
I'm a scoundrel straw hat, can't you see?
Don't do it!
You deserve better than this!
I'm no good for you!
After all this time, I finally have the key to Captain John's secrets, and I owe it all to you!
Thanks, buddy.
You're a real champ!
Now how do I ditch you and get the hell out of here?
Ha ha ha!
Oh, if we break through the walls here, is it like a shortcut?
I can do that!
What's wrong with you?
No!
All right.
We'll be right back.
Bye.
I do hope Luffy is safe. I warned him to stay out of trouble, but that may have been in vain.
Breaking your brother out will be challenging enough, but if you get captured as well, who knows what horrors you might face.
One wrong step and you may never see the light of day again.
I know you want to save Ace, but this is dangerous. Please, take care of yourself, too.
I won't let you down. You have my word. Thanks for everything, Hancock. You're the best.
Hancock. Hancock. Hancock.
Oh, my love. I can hear your angelic voice echoing through the chambers of my heart.
Okie dokie. Almost there.
Ooh, that was a good one, wasn't it?
Our jailers are certainly skilled at what they do.
Did you hear that, Empress? No? Well, worry not, milady. There are plenty more blood-curdling screams where those came from.
If you don't have a taste for sadism yet, it will do our darndest to change your mind before this little visit has come to an end.
Silence, you a person fool! You interrupted my romantic reverie!
I thought I was being polite, but she's stepping on me. This might require a new approach.
Please, Empress. He means well.
Actually, this is kind of hot.
Oops! I said that out loud, didn't I?
What the hell is going on in here?
That clown is bugging the escaped prisoner.
But who is that other guy?
Oh, no. This is the guard room.
If we keep going this way, I'm in trouble.
For crap's sake, please stop!
This place is crazy. I mean, there's a forest in the prison?
And why is everything all red?
Who are those guys down there?
They're prisoners, stupid.
This so-called forest is a torture chamber.
Every leaf is as sharp as a razor.
That's why they call them blade trees.
And the grass is made of spikes that prick you like needles.
It's called spiked needle grass.
Original, I know.
The jailers release venomous spiders
and chase the prisoners up and down the forest all day long.
Deadly pitchforks behind them,
piercing needles beneath them,
and cutting razors everywhere else.
They run until they're drenched in their own blood,
suffering agonies they never thought possible.
This is level one, otherwise known as the Crimson Hell.
The true face of Impel Dao!
Haven't I suffered enough?
You're gonna kill me!
Wow, this place really is like hell.
Are they doing this kind of stuff to ace, too?
Don't think about it.
Just keep falling.
That's dumb.
We're gonna get cut.
Oh, yeah.
Watch this!
Listen up, kid.
Now take my feet
and throw them down on the ground right below us.
Are you sure?
Okay.
Holy crap, you don't see that every day.
Whoa!
Careful!
Are you kidding me?
This is a cinch.
And the good news is
we don't need to go down any stairs
to get to the next level.
No stairs, no gate, no key,
just free falling.
The normal prisoners wouldn't want to take it,
but there is one way to get out of the Crimson Hell
that'll be perfect for our little black.
Okay, I'll take your word for it.
See?
We're already here.
Huh?
Whoa!
I can't see a thing!
Like I said,
there's a way out,
but nobody wants to take it.
Can you guess why?
It's not because it's dark and scary.
It's because this hole
is a one-way trip down to level two.
And if you think things are bad here,
well, you ain't seen nothing yet, kiddo.
When people get sent to hell,
you better believe
they'll try to claw their way out.
But no one in their right mind
would ever dream
of diving further into the abyss.
Yeah, I get it.
And it's a good thing we're crazy.
So just jump down, huh?
Yeah, but be careful.
There's a...
Are you kidding me?
Whoa, it's deep!
What do you think's down there?
Jeez.
Would you give it a minute, kid?
You got huge balls
or just a tiny brain?
Well, this works out for me.
Now I can blow this joint
and he can't say a damn thing.
Ha, ha, ha.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
I got the key to the treasure.
I got that chump off my back
and soon I'll be free.
I'd say see you in hell, buddy.
But I've been there and done that.
I robbed you, got my revenge
and you thanked me for it.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Stupid, you can't chop me.
What do you think the chop-chop fruit is for?
Heh.
Crap.
Those are my feet.
Nope, no!
They shoot me.
Crap.
Surveillance room, come in.
We sighted another escapee.
He and Buggy both fell to level two.
Can you find him?
I'm on it.
Hey, is it just me?
Or do the beasts seem kind of restless today?
As long as they're not hungry, anything but that.
I'm too tired to be afraid anymore, I don't even care.
I'm going to be there dinner sooner or later, it might as well be today, I suppose.
Oh.
Come up.
Luffy and Buggy make their way to level two, where the wild beasts of hell dwell.
And they soon find that the strange creatures live up to their reputation.
Meanwhile, Hancock reaches the heart of the prison and is greeted by none other than the warden, Magellan.
On the next, One Piece, the strongest man in the prison, Poison Man Magellan appears.
I'm going to be king of the pirates.